cea.gov.sg 2019-04-08

# Privacy Statement

1\. This is the Council for Estate Agencies corporate website. 

2\. If you are only browsing this website, we do not capture data that allows us to identify you individually.

  3\. If you choose to make an application or send us an e-mail, CEA may collect personal information from you to administer CEA's operations and services.

4\. We may share necessary data with other Government agencies, so as to serve you in the most efficient and effective manner unless such sharing is prohibited by law.

5\. We will not share your personal data with non-Government entities, except where such entities have been authorised to carry out specific Government services. 

6.  For your convenience, we may also display to you data that you have previously supplied to us or to other Government agencies. This will speed up the transaction and save you the trouble of repeating previous submissions. Should the data be out-of-date, please supply us the latest data. 

7.  To safeguard your personal data, all electronic storage and transmission of personal data are secured with appropriate security technologies. 

8.  This site may contain links to non-Government sites whose data protection and privacy practices may differ from ours. We are not responsible for the content and privacy practices of these other websites and encourage you to consult the privacy notices of those sites. 

9.   Please email us at [feedback@cea.gov.sg](mailto:feedback@cea.gov.sg), if you:

(a)    have any enquiries or feedback on our data protection policies and procedures;  
(b)    need more information on or access to data which you have provided to us in the past.
